Ismay, Lou; Papers ua902.064
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1964; 1966; 1968-1977; Undated; 5; 6.71 cubic ft.
  - Environmental Legislation Study Group, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Environmental Needs, 1972 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Environmental News, 1971; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Environmental Opinion of 1974 Gubanatorial Election (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby, 1972; 1973; 1974 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby, 1974 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby Bills, Proposals, Memos, 1973 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby Communications, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby, Newsletter, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby Notes, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby Receipts, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Environmental Resources Course General Introduction, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Environmental Studies Program, 1971 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Environmental Studies Program, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Environmental Studies Program Termination Notice, 1977 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Environmental Studies Programs of Various Universities, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Environmental Studies Summer Classes, 1975 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Environmental Teach-in, 1970 April 22 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Environmental Television, 1973 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Environmental Views and Thought, 1970-1971 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - EPDA Faculty Workshop in Environmental Education at Miami Dade Junior College, 1972 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Federal Assistance and Proposals, 1974 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Federal Energy Administration, 1976 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - First Annual New York State Environmental Education Conference, 1971 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Friends of the Earth, 1971 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - The Garden Way Platform, 1970 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Goldstein, Martin Technology and Environmental Planning, 1970 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Grants and Funds, 1970-1971 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Guilderland Central Schools, 1970-1973 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Handout Samples, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Helping the Environment, 1971; 1977 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Hudson River Pollution, 1971 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Hudson River Sloop, 1971-1973; 1975 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Hudson River Sloop Restoration with Pete Seeger Letters, 1972-1974 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Insecticide Resistance The Suffolk County Experience, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - The Institute of Man and Science, 1972-1973 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - The Institute of Man and Science, 1972-1974 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Interstate 88, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - An Introduction to the Basic Rules of Evidence, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Introduction to Legal Research, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Jobs and Grants, 1970 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Journal List, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Man and Environment Proposal, 1970 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Man and his Environment A syllabus, 1971 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Map of Property Ownership in the Mohawk Valley, 1775 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - McKinley, Daniel Publications, 1964; 1978; 1969 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - McKinley, Daniel Some Thoughts on a Second-Field in Environmental Studies, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Menus, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Movie List from 1910s-1930s, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Mt. Marcy Trail Erosion, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Nader, Ralph The Toilet Training of Industry, 1970 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - National Endowment of the Arts, 1973 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - National Speleological Society, 1974 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Nature Conservancy, 1970-1971; 1977 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - The Nature Conservancy Eastern NY Chapter, 1974 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - New York Environmental Voter's Guide, 1974 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - New York State Environmental Education Plan, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - New York State Nature & Historical Preserve Trust, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - News Clippings, 1970-1971; 1974; 1977 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - NYS Wild Scenic & Recreational Rivers System Act, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Organizations: Alphabetical list, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Organizations: Letters Received, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Organizations, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Paper Recycling, 1969; Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - PCB Case, 1976 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Personal Notes of Lou Ismay, Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Photo Resist Workshop, Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - The Pine Barrens Preserve Resolution, Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Pinebush Operation, 1971 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Pinebush Preservation, 1972; 1975 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1971-1972 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Planning for Environmental Quality, Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Population, 1969-1973 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Population, 1969-1973 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Population Articles, 1970; 1973 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Power Plant at SUNYA, 1972-1973 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Preservation the Capital Region, 1974; 1975; 1977 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Pre-Teach In Conference, 1970 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Printed Education Material, 1970 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Printing Procedures, 1971 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Propane and Methane Power, Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Proposal Lecture Services, 1975 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Proposal Post Secondary Education, 1973 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Optimum Population Resource Utilization and Environment by Jon Roland, Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Railroad Preservation, 1973 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Receipts, Bills, 1971; 1972; 1974 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Recycle Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Recycling, 1973 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Regional Planning, 1971 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Research Proposal, 1970 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Resumes, Undated (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Rotenone, 1973 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - The S + H Foundation, Inc., 1972; 1974 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - SASU, 1973-1975 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - SASU, 1975 (Box 5 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Science for Society Study Guides, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Sierra Club, 1974 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Snyder, Gary Four Changes, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Soil Map of Erie County, New York, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Solar Heating and Cooling Equipment for a School in Atlanta, Design Report, 1974 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Source List, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - State Budget Cuts on others SUNY Environmental Studies Programs, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Street Academy Course Catalogue, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - SUNYA Courses Related to the Environment, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - The SUNYA Environmental Studies Proposal including Project Research in the Five Rivers Area, 1971 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - SWEEP, 1973 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Thank you card from First Unitarium Society, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Tivoli Lakes Nature Preserve, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Tobin Articles, 1970 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Transportation and Interstate 88, 1970 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Transportation, 1973 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Unique Area Priority Rating Report: Knox Cave and Mt. Ida, 1974 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - United Teaching Profession, 1971 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - The Village of Altamont and the Bank, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Water Testing Equipment, 1973 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Watercraft Pollution Control, 1973 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Water Standards, 1971 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Watervliet Shaker Historic and Recreation District, Undated (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Waterways, 1973-1975 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - A Week with Isaac Asimov, 1975 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Youth Services, 1971 (Box 6 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Citizen's Workshop on Atomic Energy at SUNYA, 1973 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Clip Art, Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - The Environmental Crunch Senator Pete Domenici, 1974 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Environmental Information Request 1980 Winter Olympics, 1975 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Environmental Planning Lobby, 1975-1976 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Environmental Teach-In Booklist, 1970 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - New York State Assembly Memos, 1976 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Pamphlets on the Hudson River, Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Save the Pine Bush Sticker, Undated (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Senate Environmental Teach-in, 1975-1976 (Box 7 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Arbor Hill Project No. 1: Urban Renewal Area Albany, New York, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Clearwater, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Maps, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Ephemera, 5.219
    - Environmental Studies Styrofoam Label, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
    - "Future: a game of strategy, influence and chance", 1966 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
    - Morgan, Dan, "Village of Iola", Undated; photograph with hard backing (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
    - Wooden stamp of SUNYA fine arts address, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1968-1977; Undated; 6; 1 cubic foot
  Administrative, business, and student mail form the majority of the correspondence series. The student mail consists of letters from Ismay's former students. One of the folders is restricted due to privacy concerns.
  - Administrative, 1968-1974 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Administrative, 1969-1972 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Administrative, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Administrative, 1970-1974 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Administrative, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Administrative, 1974-1977 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 6-7)
  - Administrative, Undated (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Business Mail, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Business Mail, 1971-1974 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Business Mail, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 11-12)
  - Business Mail, 1974-1977 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 13-14)
  - Environmental Forum Mail, 1974-1975; 1977 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Environmental Studies Memo's Eugene McLaren, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Request of Information, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Student Mail, 1970-1973 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Student Mail, 1970-1977 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 19-22)
  - Student Mail, Undated (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Student Mail -- Personal, 1973-1974; 1976 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 24)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted.
  - Thank you Letters, 1975 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Third Party Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Time Magazine -- Returned Material, 1970 (Box 1 (6-Correspondence), Folder 27)
    Includes Photographs.
- Publications, 1959; 1964; 1966; 1968-1977; Undated; 7; 3 cubic ft.
  This series includes material about Ismay and the Albany area in publication form. Literature on specific scientific topics, newsletters, publications from other faculty members such as Vincent Schaefer, and State University of New York at Albany publications make up the bulk of the series.
  - 1975 Directory (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Activist Reader, 1975 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Administrative Action for Interstate Route 88, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Agreement: Between The State of New York + Senate Professional Association, Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
  - An Air Pollution Resource Manual for Junior High School and High School Teachers, The Research Foundation of SUNY, 1971 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Albany City Record: Excavation Laws, 1974 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Albany Student Press, 1971 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Alumni House Conference Center, Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
  - American Association of Museums, 1969-1972 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Annual Report of the Committee on Environmental Conservation, 1975 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Application for Grants Under Environmental Education Program, 1977 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Artists at SUNY Albany, 1972-1974; Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Assessment of Courses and Teachers, 1975 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Associated Council of the Arts, 1971 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Campus Courier, 1969 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Capital District Windmill Fleet # 41 Newsletter, 1973 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
  - The Challenge of the Environment: A Primer on EPA's Statutory Authority, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Characteristics of New York Lakes, 1970 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Chronica (Newsletter), 1974 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Commercial Courier, 1970 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
  - The Conservation Foundation Annual Report, 1969 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Cornell University Program on Science Technology and Society Curriculum Innovation, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Directory Nature and Environmental Education Centers in NY State, 1977 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Directory of Nature Centers, Outdoor Study Areas and Environmental Education Centers in NYS, 1974 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Diving into History, 1969 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
  - Drug Abuse Literature, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
  - Ecological Resources in NY State's Colleges and Universities, 1971 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
  - Electrostatistics Selected Classified Bibliography, 1973 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
  - An Energy Tax and Other Essays on the Financing of Education, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 29)
  - Environmental Action, 1971 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 30)
  - Environmental Education: Academia's Response, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 31)
  - Environmental Education Act, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 32)
  - Environmental Education Handbook, Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 33)
  - Environmental Education Instructional Activities, 1970 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 34)
  - Environmental Education The State Education Department, Albany, 1971 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 35)
  - An Environmental Experience, 1971 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 36)
  - Environmental Forum Bibliography State University of New York at Albany, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 37)
  - The Esoteric Entrepreneur as A Revolutionary of the Right His Crooked way and the road to Eupsychia, Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 38)
  - The Experimental Studies Program, 1973 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 39)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 40)
  - Farm, Substance, and Difference, 1970 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 41)
  - Geology and Hydrology of the West Milton Area Saratoga County, New York, 1964 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 42)
  - A Guide to Environmental Literature in the SUNYA Library, Undated (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 43)
  - Highway Map of Albany County, New York, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Hillside Show: History of Altamont, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
  - The Hudson: Biological Resources, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Inside Education, 1971 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Johnson Hall, 1971 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Journal of the NY State School Boards Association, Inc, 1973 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Lake George Historical Association, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
  - May, Hayden B. Improving Quality of Environment through Environment Behavior Studies: An Annotated Bibliography, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
  - The Medical Center Perceived by Dan Budnik, 1974 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Moderator, 1969 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
  - The Mohawk Valley and the American Revolution, 1972 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
  - The Nature Conservancy, News, Fall 1975 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
  - New York Environmental News 1973, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
  - New Your State Environment 1974, 1976 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
  - New York State Environmental Education Plan, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
  - New York State Environmental Plan by D.E.C., 1972 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
  - New York State Museum and Science Service, 1973 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Newsletter on Science, Technology & Human Values, 1977 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Newsletters, 1974; 1975; 1976; 1977 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Observation A Magazine of the Visual Arts, 1972 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Organic Guide to Colleges and Universities, 1973 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Pamphlets of NY Wildlife, 1970; Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Parks, Recreation & Open Space, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Plaat, Mark Energy, Ecology and the City, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Policies of the Board of Trustees: State University of New York, 1974 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
  - Potential Natural vegetation as an Indicator for Land use Thesis, by Steven Jeffrey Anthony, 1971 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
  - Practical Program for Protecting The Environment, 1970 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
  - Primer, 1970 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
  - Programs for Geographical Analysis: Department of Geography, SUNY at Albany, 1974 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 29)
  - Progress Report Residential Market Analysis, Part V, 1968 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 30)
  - Purpose and Function of the University, 1970 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 31)
  - Recycling of Tin Free Steel Cans, Tin Cansand Scrap, by E.J. Ostrowski, 1971 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 32)
  - Renshaw, Edward A note on Private Goods and Public Bads, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 33)
  - Report of the Subcommittee on Biology in Public Affairs, 1970 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 34)
  - Reports by Edward Renshaw, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 35)
  - Requirements of the U.S. Food Drug, Cosmetic Act, 1970 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 36)
  - Reviews and Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 37)
  - Rodent Publications, 1964; 1969; 1970; Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 38)
  - RPI A Project to Build: Educational Bridges Between Science and the Humanities, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications), Folder 39)
  - Saturday Review of Education, 1973 March (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Save Schoharie Valley: Stop the Dams!, Undated (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Scenic and recreational Development: Hudson River... Riverfront Arterial, 1970 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Schaefer, Vincent Articles, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Science Policy and the Universities of The Empire State, 1970 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Science Technology Related Activities in the Government of New York State, 1971 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Scientific American, 1964; 1966; 1969; 1971 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The Sculpture of Gerald DiGiusto, 1970 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Search 1-3: At the State University of New York, 1976 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Sheppard, J. Douglas -- DEC Valuation of the Hudson River Fishery Resources; Past, Present and Future, 1976 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Smoking Pamphlets, 1970; Undated (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Social Benefit Corporations? By Robert Louis Schulz, 1971 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
  - State Nature and Historical Preserve Trust by Robert E. Young, Undated (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Style Sheet for Bibliography and Footnotes, Undated (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Sulfur Pollution Abatement in the New York Electric Power Industry, 1972 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
  - SUNYA Five Rivers Project, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
  - SUNYA Publications, 1969-1970; 1973 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Support for the Arts, 1973 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
  - A Survey of the Ecological Resources within Academic Institutions in the State of NY, 1970 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
  - A Survey of Environmental Science Organizations in the U.S.A., 1970 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Synthesis, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1976 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
  - A Teachers Packet For Conservation Information and Education, Undated (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
  - TETE: Total Education in the Total Environment, 1971 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Tower Tribune: A proposed Statement of Mission, 1976 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Town of Brunswick Conservation Advisory Council Annual Report, 1976 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
  - Urban Morality, 1973 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
  - Waite, Diana 19th Century Tin Roofing, 1971 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
  - Water & Waste Digest, 1975 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
  - Waterways Project Part One, 1973 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 29)
  - The Yale Review, 1959 (Box 3 (7-Publications), Folder 30)